Redfin Privacy Policy
=====================

**Effective Date: January 1, 2020**

**Updated: April 17, 2023**

This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information processed by Redfin in the course of our business, including, Redfin.com, Redfin.ca, the Redfin Applications, as well as additional sites/applications that link to this Privacy Policy and are operated by our affiliates and subsidiaries including Redfin Ventures, Inc., Redfin Home Services LLC, Walkscore, and Title Forward (each a "**Site**") and the services provided through the Sites (collectively with the Sites, the "**Services**").

The terms "**Redfin**," "**we**," "**us**," and "**our**" includes Redfin Corporation and our affiliates and subsidiaries (including, without limitation, Redfin Unlimited Liability Company for individuals located in Canada).

Please note that unless we define a term in this Privacy Notice, capitalized terms used in this Privacy Notice have the same meanings as in our [Terms of Use](https://www.redfin.com/about/terms-of-use). By using our Services, you acknowledge that your Personal Information will be handled as described in this Privacy Notice. Your use of our Services and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Privacy Notice and our [Terms of Use](https://www.redfin.com/about/terms-of-use), including their applicable terms governing limitations on damages, and the resolution of disputes.

This Privacy Notice contains the following sections:

1\. Personal Information Collection and Use
-------------------------------------------

This Privacy Policy covers our use of Personal Information. "**Personal Information**," means any information that relates to you and can -- either on its own or in combination with other information -- identify you as an individual. Personal information does not include information that has been de-identified or aggregated such that you can no longer be identified.

The types of information we collect depends on your level of engagement with the Services. The more you interact with the Services, the more information we need to provide the Services. This Section explains how we collect and use personal information based on your level of engagement with the Services.

### A. All Users of the Redfin Sites and Applications

From registered and unregistered users of the Sites, we automatically receive and record information whenever you interact with the Sites. This includes IP address data from our server logs, cookie information, browser information, information about your activity while on the Sites (such as the pages you request, properties that you view or save, and property that you claim), and the URL of the site you came to the Sites from. We also may collect the mobile device ID (such as the ID for Advertising on iOS and Android ID on Android) from users of the Redfin Applications. If permitted by the settings on your device and/or with your consent, we will also collect your geo-location information. We use this to provide you with location-specific information, such as homes for sale near your current location as determined by your geolocation, and information about listing your home for sale based on your geolocation. We may also approximate your location based on your IP address, to customize your experience on our Sites.

We may also use the information listed above to help diagnose problems and performance with the Services, analyze trends, customize your experience, and administer the Services. We may provide IP addresses to third-parties to help us analyze website user survey data. We may also use the information described in this section to better target information about Redfin's Sites and Services, for example, by displaying more accurate or relevant information on our Sites, matching you to a public record listing of a property, tailoring the advertising we display on third party websites and platforms, and sending better targeted and tailored messages, including via email and/or push notifications.

### B. Registered Users of the Redfin Sites and Applications

We are required to collect certain information, including your name and email address, as a condition of our licenses with the multiple real estate listing services (the "**MLSs**") in order to allow you to access the full MLS listings. You give us this information when you create your Redfin account. When you give us this information at one of our events, or upon your request, we will create a Redfin account for you, and you agree that this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use apply. In addition, when you are signed into your Redfin account and using Redfin through Facebook, Twitter, or any other third-party authorization service, we may make use of the information that they provide us to further customize your Redfin experience. We may share Personal Information with such third parties to deliver Redfin tailored content both on our Services and on third party sites (e.g., social media sites).

* **My Redfin**: My Redfin is a feature that allows you to upload notes and photos about a property, save searches, add favorites and x-outs, and otherwise organize homes that may interest you. We save all of this "My Redfin" information for use later in connection with our Services. It is stored with your Redfin account information.
    
* **Account Password Security**: Your Redfin account password is encrypted on our server. It is your responsibility not to disclose your password to other people and to ensure you maintain its security.
    
* **Account Updates**: By visiting your [My Redfin: Account Settings](https://www.redfin.com/myredfin/settings), you can correct, amend, add or delete Personal Information associated with your account. However, even after you update information, we may maintain a copy of the original information in our records as required by applicable law or other legal obligation.

### C. Home Tours, Real Estate Classes, and other In-Person Meetings

When you submit a home tour request, we will ask for your tour date and time preferences, as well as your phone number. We may ask for similar information when you request or attend a home buying or selling class, or when you request or attend a strategy session or similar in-person meeting with a Redfin agent. We may also ask some questions so that our agent can verify your identity, and such information will be used to register you for a Redfin account. When you meet up with one of our agents, the agent may ask you to verify your identity and may even ask to see a photo ID.

### D. Redfin Clients

When you are getting ready to buy or sell a home and you start working with our coordinators and agents, you become a Redfin client. As part of the home purchase or sale process, you will need to provide a lot of information as is customary for a home purchase or sale transaction. This information can include, without limitation, your name, address, phone number, email address, financial or payment information, including without limitation, buyer loan pre-approval documentation and seller property information. We ask you, as a buyer, for loan pre-approvals from a mortgage broker or lender to determine which homes are in your price range and to help you make an offer more quickly when you do find a home. You, as a seller, may be legally required to disclose certain information about your property to prospective buyers. Once you sign a listing agreement or buyer agreement with us, your relationship with Redfin is governed by that agreement, as well as our online [Terms of Use](https://www.redfin.com/about/terms-of-use) and this Privacy Policy.

### E. Communications with Redfin

Redfin may collect Personal Information from you such as email address, phone number, or mailing address when you request information about our Services, register for our newsletter, request customer or technical support, or otherwise communicate with us.

### F. Marketing

We may send marketing materials to Redfin account holders and clients using various communication channels, including without limitation, email, text messages/SMS, push notifications, telephone calls, and direct mail. Individuals may also subscribe to Listing Alert Emails or other notifications with information such as customized summaries of homes for sale. Redfin may send you Redfin-related news and surveys in accordance with applicable law.

### G. Call Recording

We may record any telephone calls between you and our agents or other representatives for training and quality assurance purposes.

### H. Surveys

Redfin may contact you to participate in surveys. If you decide to participate, you may be asked to provide certain information, which may include Personal Information.

### I. Sharing with Friends or Colleagues

Redfin's Services may allow you to forward or share certain content with a friend or colleague, such as an email inviting your friend to use our Services. Email addresses that you may provide for a friend or colleague will be used to send your friend or colleague the content or link you request in accordance with applicable law.

### J. Interactive Features

Redfin may offer interactive features such as chat services, forums, and social media pages. We may collect the information you submit or make available through these features. Any content you provide on the public sections of these channels will be considered "public" and will not be subject to the privacy protections referenced herein.

### K. De-Identified and Aggregated Information

We may use Personal Information and other information about you to create de-identified and/or aggregated information, such as de-identified demographic information, de-identified location information, de-identified or aggregated trends, reports, or statistics, information about the computer or device from which you access our Services, or other analyses we create. De-identified and aggregated information is used for a variety of functions, including the measurement of visitors' interest in and use of various portions or features of the Sites and Services. De-identified and aggregated information is not Personal Information, and we may use and disclose such information in a number of ways, including research, internal analysis, analytics, and any other legally permissible purpose.

### L. Conferences and Trade Shows

We may attend or participate in conferences and trade shows where we collect Personal Information from individuals who interact with or express an interest in Redfin and/or the Services. If you provide us with any information at one of these events, we will use it for the purposes for which it was collected.

### M. Information We Collect Automatically

We may collect certain information automatically when you use the Services. This information may include your Internet protocol (IP) address, user settings, IMEI, MAC address, cookie identifiers, mobile carrier, mobile advertising and other unique identifiers, details about your browser, operating system or device, location information, Internet service provider, pages that you visit before, during and after using the Services, information about the links you click, and other information about how you use the Services. Information we collect may be associated with accounts and other devices.

### N. Information from Other Sources

We may obtain information about you from other sources, including through third-party services and organizations to supplement information provided by you. This supplemental information allows us to verify information that you have provided to us and to enhance our ability to provide you with the Services.

### O. Other Uses of Information

In addition to the specific collection and uses listed above, we may use any of the Personal Information we collect for the following business purposes:

* to operate our Sites and provide our Services in accordance with our [Terms of Use](https://www.redfin.com/about/terms-of-use) and/or any other agreement you may have with us;
* to manage your Personal Information and accounts;
* to respond to your questions or inquiries;
* to conduct promotional activities, including contests or surveys;
* to undertake internal research for technological development and demonstration;
* to improve, upgrade or enhance our Sites and Services;
* to send you informational or promotional communications;
* to detect bugs, security incidents (including to protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecute those responsible for that activity);
* for fraud prevention and detection purposes;
* to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;
* to undertake activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a Service, Site or transaction;
* to carry out other purposes that are disclosed to you and/or to which you consent; and
* for any other lawful business operations or business purposes.

2\. Personal Information Sharing
--------------------------------

While we do not exchange your Personal Information with others for monetary consideration, we may share your Personal Information with the following categories of third parties as part of our Services to you or to assist us in conducting our marketing and advertising, or for other business or commercial purposes listed above in this Privacy Policy.

### A. Public Record Information

Please be aware that home sales and purchases may be a matter of public record, and your name and address, the price you paid, your property taxes, and other information may be available from public sites regardless of the brokerage(s), if any, who assist in the transaction. We post on our Sites some information that typically becomes part of the public record of a home sale or purchase.

### B. Non-Public Record Information

We share information obtained from you, MLSs and other third-party sources that is not on the public record to facilitate your home purchase or sale transaction. This includes:

* **Service Providers to all Redfin Clients**: Our agents work with third parties to process your home search and sale transaction and must share your information with those third parties. Examples include MLSs and providers of software used for document preparation and electronic signing.
    
* **Partner Agents**: A Partner Agent is employed by or works with another brokerage and is not a representative or employee of Redfin. Partner Agents have contracted with us to provide Redfin-quality service to a wider range of customers. We'll refer you to a Partner Agent at our discretion. If you are referred to a Partner Agent for your home purchase or sale transaction, we share your information with that Partner Agent so they can assist you. Redfin is not responsible for the work performed or the services provided by Partner Agents in any manner.
    
* **Home Seller Service Providers**: As is customary as your home sales agent, we share your listing information with MLSs and other listing websites, such as Realtor.com, Trulia.com and Zillow.com. As a result, your listing may appear on more than one website. We may also share your listing and contact information with listing vendors such as photographers, home staging experts and home repair professionals like plumbers and electricians, as needed.
    
* **Home Buyer Service Providers**: As is customary as your home purchase agent, we must share your buying information with inspectors, title companies, escrow agents, closing attorneys, lenders, and other third parties as needed to process your transaction.
    
* **Potential Buyers**: By law, we are required to disclose certain information about your property to potential buyers.

### C. Negotiations

We also post price offers and counteroffers on our Sites. We do not post your name on our Sites without your permission, but if the sale is closed, the price and the fact that you bought or sold your house at that price may be a matter of public record.

### D. Redfin Corporate Family

We may share your information with members of the Redfin family of entities for various purposes, including to: (i) provide the Services to you; (ii) help detect and prevent potentially illegal and fraudulent acts and other violations of our policies and agreements; (iii) help with marketing initiatives; and (iii) manage and improve Redfin products, Sites, Services and tools.

### E. Redfin Requests

Through the Services, you can make a request to tour a home, get in contact with a real estate agent, receive help selling or buying a home, or submit other requests. When you make such a request through Redfin, you authorize Redfin to share your Personal Information including your contact information, home search history, favorites and saved searches, with a real estate professional (a Redfin Agent or staff member, or a Partner Agent) for the purpose of responding to your request.

### F. Service Providers

We may share your Personal Information with third-party service providers that assist us in providing the Services. We use reasonable efforts to do so with the appropriate contractual protection in place to ensure that your Personal Information is protected and used only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### G. Business Partners

We may provide Personal Information to business partners to provide you with a product or service you have requested. We may also provide Personal Information to business partners with whom we jointly offer products or services in accordance with applicable law.

### H. Cookies and Similar Technologies

Our Services may use site and app Technologies (including cookies, web-beacons, javascripts, software development kids, and other technologies) to collect and share Personal Information about you, your device, and your use of our Services for any of our business purposes described in this Privacy Policy. These Technologies may include (a) Redfin cookies we put your device's browser to help us keep track of when you were last on the Sites, and what you last searched on the Sites, (b) first- and third-party cookies and Technologies for analytics and experience enhancement, such as comScore and Google, to help us analyze how people are using the Services or personalize your experience, and (c) Technologies from the interest-based and other ad providers described immediately below in [Section 2.I.](#i-targeted-and-interest-based-ad-providers)(“Targeted and Interest-Based Ad Providers). For information on rights you may have to opt-out of data collection or sharing by such Technologies used on our Services, see [Section 3.C.](#c-opting-out-of-technologies-and-tracking) below (“Opting-Out of Technologies and Tracking”).

### I. Targeted and Interest-Based Ad Providers

We may share the information that we collect about you with others (including advertising networks and service providers) to tailor and serve you ads on our Services, as well as other websites and social media networks. This practice is commonly referred to as "interest-based advertising" or "online behavioral advertising." These advertising networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of Technologies (e.g., cookies, web-beacons and other methods). This allows Redfin to target our advertising to you through demographic, behavioral and contextual means. As a result, you may see ads for Redfin on other websites and social media.

### J. APIs and SDKs

We may use third-party APIs and software development kits ("SDKs") as part of the functionality of our Services. APIs and SDKs may allow third parties, including advertising partners, to collect your Personal Information to provide our Service-related content that is more relevant to you. For more information about our use of APIs and SDKs, please contact us as set forth below.

### K. Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, purchase or sale of assets, or transition of service to another provider, then your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction as permitted by law and/or contract.

### L. Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate: (i) to respond to claims or legal processes (including subpoenas); (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the property, rights and safety of a third party or the public in general; and (iii) to stop any activity that we consider illegal, unethical or legally actionable.

### M. Other Purposes

Redfin may share your Personal Information for other purposes that are clearly disclosed to you at the time you provide Personal Information or with your consent.

3\. Your Choices
----------------

### A. General

You may have the right to opt in or opt out of certain uses of your Personal Information, as described below. Even if you opt out, we may still collect and use Personal Information regarding your activities on our Sites, Services and/or information from the advertisements on third party websites for other legal purposes as described above in accordance with applicable law.

### B. Electronic Messages, Phone Calls and other Communications

If you receive an unwanted email from Redfin, you can visit the Email Preferences section of your [My Redfin: Alerts & Emails](https://www.redfin.com/myredfin/alerts-settings) or use the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email to opt out of receiving future emails. Note that you will continue to receive transaction-related emails regarding products or Services you have requested. We may also send you certain non-promotional communications regarding us and our Services, and you will not be able to opt out of those communications (e.g., communications regarding the Services or updates to our [Terms of Use](https://www.redfin.com/about/terms-of-use) or this Privacy Policy).

### C. Opting-Out of Technologies and Tracking

* **Opting Out of Redfin's Interest-Based Advertising**: If you do not want Redfin to collect, use and share information about you to deliver interest-based advertising, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and follow the opt-out instructions. Please note that most opt-out mechanisms are cookie-based and will only affect the specific computer and browser that is used to submit an opt-out request. If you have multiple computers or change computers, or use multiple browsers, you will need to submit opt-out requests for each such computer or browser. In addition, if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, you will need to renew the opt-out choices to ensure that any opt-out cookies remain effective.  
      
    We may also share information that we collect from you, such as your email (in hashed form) with LiveRamp Inc. LiveRamp may convert your information into a code that can be shared with advertising companies to enable interest-based and targeted advertising. To opt out of this use, please click here.
    
* **Opting Out of Interest-Based Advertising Generally**: The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt out of receiving targeted ads from data partners and other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. You can access these, and also learn more about targeted advertising and consumer choice and privacy, at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/), [https://youradchoices.ca/choices/](https://youradchoices.ca/choices/), and [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). To separately make choices for mobile apps on a mobile device, you can download DAA's AppChoices application from your device's app store. Please note you must separately opt out in each browser and on each device.
    
* **Google Analytics**: We use the Google Analytics service to provide us with demographic data about our users on a de-identified basis. This Google service uses a cookie that can be recognized by Google or its affiliate DoubleClick when you visit other websites. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You can opt out of Google Analytics' collection and use of data generated by your use of the Services by going to [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
    
* **Browser Solutions for Disabling Cookies**: If you wish to prevent cookies from tracking your activity on our website or visits across multiple websites, you can set your browser to block certain cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your device from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Visitors to our Sites who disable cookies will be able to browse the Sites, but some features may not function.
    
* **Opting Out of Mobile Device ID Tracking**: We may use the information that we collect about you (whether directly from our Sites, from our Applications, through your device(s), or from a third party) to help us and our third-party service providers identify other devices that you use (e.g., a mobile phone, tablet, other computer, etc.). We and our third-party service providers also may use the cross-device use and other information we learn about you to serve targeted advertising on your devices and to send you emails. Mobile device users may opt out of receiving some interest-based advertising in their mobile apps by following the instructions for [Android](https://support.google.com/googleplay/android-developer/answer/6048248?hl=en) and [iOS](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074). Please note that precise instructions may vary by device.
    
* **Do Not Track**: Do Not Track ("**DNT**") is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. Please note that we do not respond to or honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.

### D. Mobile Devices

We may send you push notifications through the Redfin mobile application. You may at any time opt-out from receiving these types of communications by changing the settings on your mobile device. Redfin may also collect location-based information if you use our mobile applications. You may opt-in or opt-out of this collection by changing the settings on your mobile device.

### E. Delete your Account

You may delete your Redfin account on your [My Redfin: Account Settings](https://www.redfin.com/myredfin/settings) page under "Close Account" section. We retain Personal Information for as long as we have a valid business purpose to or to meet our legal obligations. Redfin may be required to keep a copy of your Personal Information in accordance with Section 5 below.

4\. Monitoring of our Services
------------------------------

We may monitor any and all use of our Services, and may capture and retain information and records reflecting your activity on our Services for our business purposes. This may include all of the “Information We Collect Automatically” described in [Section 1.M.](#m-information-we-collect-automatically) above, server logs, cookie information, browser information, your communications with Redfin or otherwise sent or submitted using our Service, and any other information about your activity or actions while on or using the Services (such as, without limitation, the pages you view, links you click or other actions you take with your mouse, videos you watch while on our sites, properties that you view or save, property that you claim, and the URL of the site you came to the Services from).

The Technologies used in connection with our Services (such as cookies, web-beacons, javascripts, software development kids, and others) described above in [Section 2.H.](#h-cookies-and-similar-technologies) (“Cookies and Similar Technologies”), may also collect the foregoing information reflecting your use of and activity on our Services, or may enable our third-party service providers or partners to collect such information. Similarly, we may disclose any of the information we capture by monitoring the activity on our Services to one or more third parties for our business purposes. Further, if you interact with chat functionalities on our Services, what you enter may be captured and retained by us and our third-party partners for our business purposes. If you type information into forms or other fields on our Services, what you enter may be captured and retained by us and our third-party partners for our business purposes.

By using our Services, you consent to our monitoring of our Services. If you do not consent to the monitoring of our Services described here, you should not use our Services.

5\. Individual Rights in Personal Information
---------------------------------------------

In accordance with applicable law, you may have the right to: (i) request confirmation of whether we are processing your Personal Information; (ii) obtain access to or a copy of your Personal Information; (iii) receive an electronic copy of Personal Information that you have provided to us, or ask us to send that information to another company (the "right of data portability"); (iv) restrict our uses of your Personal Information; (v) seek correction or amendment of inaccurate, untrue, incomplete, or improperly processed Personal Information; and (vi) request erasure of Personal Information held about you by Redfin, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us as set forth below.

We will process such requests in accordance with applicable laws. To protect your privacy, Redfin may take steps to verify your identity before fulfilling your request. We collect and report annual metrics on how we respond to requests: [Redfin Privacy Metrics](https://www.redfin.com/privacy-metrics)

6\. Personal Information Retention
----------------------------------

Redfin retains the information we receive as described in this Privacy Policy for as long as you use our Services or as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected, provide our Services, resolve disputes, establish legal defenses, conduct audits, pursue legitimate business purposes, enforce our agreements, and comply with applicable laws.

7\. Personal Information Storage and Security
---------------------------------------------

Redfin is headquartered in the United States. You agree that we may store and process the information we collect anywhere in the world, including but not limited to, the United States.

We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure.

By using the Services or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Services.

8\. Additional Information for California Residents
---------------------------------------------------

### California Privacy Notice Provisions

This section of the Privacy Policy provides additional information for California residents (“**consumer**” or “**you**”) and applies to “Personal Information,” as defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act 2018, as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act 2020 (the “**CCPA**”), whether collected online or offline. This section describes our information practices and any rights you may have regarding your Personal Information pursuant to the CCPA.

**Categories of Personal Information We Collect**

For purposes of this section, “**Personal Information**” means information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household. Please note that Personal Information **does not** include:

* Publicly available information, such as information lawfully made available from government records, information we have a reasonable basis to believe is lawfully made available to the general public by you or by widely distributed media, or by a person to whom you have disclosed the information and not restricted it to a specific audience;
    
* Deidentified or aggregated information; and
    
* Information excluded from the CCPA's scope, like:
    
    * health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data;
        
    * personal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA), and the Driver's Privacy Protection Act of 1994.

The following identifies the categories of personal information we collect about you (and have collected in the prior 12 months), as enumerated by the CCPA. Depending on how you use the Services, we collect the following categories of personal information through our Services:

* **Identifiers**. Name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, driver’s license number, Social Security, or other similar identifiers.
* **Commercial information**. Name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, driver’s license number, Social Security, or other similar identifiers.
* **Internet or other electronic network activity**. Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer's interaction with an internet website, application, or advertisement.
* **Geolocation data**. Precise geolocation information derived from a device.
* **Audio, electronic, visual, or similar information**. Includes audio, electronic, visual, or similar information, photographs, and images (e.g., that you provide us), call recordings (e.g., of customer support calls), and other visual or similar information you provide via our Services.
* **Inferences**. Such as inferences drawn from any of the information described in this section reflecting a consumer's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.
* **Sensitive personal information**. In limited circumstances, we may collect social security numbers, driver’s license, and precise geolocation.

**Categories of Sources from Which Personal Information is Collected**

Depending on how you interact with our Services, we generally collect the categories of Personal Information listed above from the following categories of sources:

* directly from the consumer;
* from our affiliates and business partners, including Partner Agents;
* from advertising networks;
* from operating systems and platforms;
* from data brokers;
* from third parties, and
* from publicly available sources, including government records.

**Retention of Personal Information**

Redfin retains the Personal Information we collect as described in this Privacy Policy for as long as you use our Services or as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected, provide our Services, resolve disputes, establish legal defenses, conduct audits, pursue legitimate business purposes, enforce our agreements, and comply with applicable laws. Rather than delete your Personal Information, we may also deidentify or it by removing identifying details. If we deidentify the data, we will not attempt to reidentify it.

**Business or Commercial Purposes for Collecting and Disclosing Personal Information**

We may use and disclose the Personal Information we collect for the following business purposes, as more fully described above:

* To operate our Sites and provide our Services in accordance with our [Terms of Use](https://www.redfin.com/about/terms-of-use) and/or any other agreement you may have with us;
* To manage your Personal Information and accounts;
* To respond to your questions or inquiries;
* To conduct promotional activities, including contests or surveys;
* To undertake internal research for technological development and demonstration;
* To improve, upgrade or enhance our Sites and Services;
* To send you informational or promotional communications;
* To detect bugs, security incidents (including to protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecute those responsible for that activity);
* To undertake activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a Service, Site or transaction;
* To carry out other purposes that are disclosed to you and/or to which you consent;
* To conduct financial, tax and accounting audits; audits and assessments of our operations, privacy, security and financial controls, risk, and compliance with legal obligations; our general business, accounting, record keeping and legal functions, and to maintain appropriate business records and enforce company policies and procedures;
* To assess and implement mergers, acquisitions, reorganizations, bankruptcies, and other business transactions such as financings; and
* To comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including as part of a judicial proceeding; to respond to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or other legal process; or as part of an investigation or request, whether formal or informal, from law enforcement or a governmental authority.

**Disclosures of Personal Information for a Business Purpose**

We may disclose your Personal Information to the third parties or others as described above in this Privacy Policy, for any of the business purposes described above in this Privacy Policy.

In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have disclosed the following categories of Personal Information in our role as a business for a business purpose:

* Identifiers;
* Commercial information;
* Internet or other electronic network activity information;
* Geolocation data;
* Audio, electronic, visual or similar information;
* Inferences; and
* Sensitive personal information

**Sensitive Personal Information**

Our collection, use, and disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information is generally limited to what is reasonable and proportionate for the following purposes:

* To perform the services or provide the goods as reasonably expected by you;
* To detect security incidents that compromise the availability, authenticity, integrity, and confidentiality of sensitive Personal Information that is stored or transmitted;
* To resist malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal actions directed at Redfin and to prosecute those responsible for those actions;
* To ensure the physical safety of you and others;
* For short-term, transient uses;
* To verify your information, provide customer support, or provide similar services; and
* With respect to a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by Redfin, to verify or maintain the quality or safety, improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device.

**Sales and Sharing of Personal Information**

The CCPA defines “sale” broadly as “disclosing or making available Personal Information to a third party in exchange for monetary or other valuable consideration,” and “sharing” as “disclosing or making available personal information to a third party for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising.” While we do not disclose personal information to third parties in exchange for monetary consideration, we may be considered to be “selling” or “sharing” certain categories of Personal Information to third parties through our use of ad companies, analytics providers, and social networks (through third party tags on our Sites) to improve and measure our ad campaigns and reach users with more relevant ads and content.

The categories of Personal Information that we may have “sold” or “shared” in the prior twelve (12) months include:

* identifiers;
* internet or other electronic network activity information;
* geolocation information; and
* inferences.

The categories of third parties under the CCPA to whom we have disclosed this information are:

* data analytics providers;
* advertising networks; and
* social networks.

We do not sell or share Personal Information about individuals we know are under age sixteen (16).

**Your CCPA Rights and Choices**

The CCPA provides consumers (California residents) with specific rights regarding their Personal Information. This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights. Subject to certain exceptions, consumers have the right to make the following requests:

**_Right to Know/Access_**. You have the right to request (up to twice per year subject to certain exemptions), free of charge, that we disclose information about our collection and use of your Personal Information, including:

* The categories of Personal Information we collected about you;
* The categories of sources from which the Personal Information is collected;
* The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that Personal Information;
* The categories of third parties with whom we disclose Personal Information; and
* The specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected.

**_Right to Correct_**. Subject to certain conditions and exceptions, you have the right to request that we correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information.

**_Right to Delete_**. Subject to certain conditions and exceptions, you have the right to request that we delete your Personal Information. Once we receive and confirm your request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your Personal Information from our records, unless an exception applies.

**_Right to Opt-Out of Sales and Sharing_**. To exercise your right to opt-out of the “sale” or “sharing” of your Personal Information, please visit our _Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information_ page [here](https://www.redfin.com/about/privacy/cookie).

You also have the right to opt-out of “sales” and “sharing” of your Personal Information through the use of an opt-out preference signal. If our Site detects that your browser or device is transmitting an opt-out preference signal, such as the “global privacy control”—or GPC— signal, we will opt that browser or device out of cookies on our Site that result in a “sale” or “sharing” of your Personal Information. If you come to our Site from a different device or from a different browser on the same device, you will need to opt-out, or use an opt-out preference signal, for that browser and/or device as well.

Please note that, if you have entered your email address on our site, to fully opt-out of “sales” and “sharing” of Personal Information you will also need to use the LiveRamp opt-out tool by clicking [here](https://optout.liveramp.com/opt_out).

**_Right to Limit Use and Disclosure_**. We do not engage in uses or disclosures of “sensitive personal information” that would trigger the _Right to Limit Use of Sensitive Personal Information_ under the CCPA.

**_Right to Non-Discrimination_**. We will not discriminate against you in terms of price or service level for exercising any of the rights described in this section.

**Exercising Your CCPA Rights**

If you are a California resident and would like to exercise your CCPA rights, you may do so via any of the methods described below:

* Emailing us at [privacy@redfin.com](mailto:privacy@redfin.com)
* Calling us at 1-844-759-7732
* Filling out our [webform](https://www.redfin.com/about/contact-us).

**_Authorized Agent_**. You may designate someone as an authorized agent to submit requests and act on your behalf. Authorized agents will be required to provide proof of their authorization in their first communication with us, and we may also require that you directly verify your identity and the authority of your authorized agent.

Businesses operating as an authorized agent on behalf of a California resident must provide both of the following:

* (1) Certificate of good standing with its state of organization; and
* (2) A written authorization document, signed by the California resident, containing the California resident’s name, address, telephone number, and valid email address, and expressly authorizing the business to act on behalf of the California resident.

Individuals operating as an authorized agent on behalf of a California resident must provide either of the following:

* (1) A notarized power of attorney signed and dated by the California resident naming the authorized agent as the California resident’s representative; or
* (2) A written authorization document, signed by the California resident, containing the California resident’s name, address, telephone number, and valid email address, and expressly authorizing the individual to act on behalf of the California resident.

We reserve the right to reject (1) authorized agents who have not fulfilled the above requirements, or (2) automated CCPA requests where we have reason to believe the security of the requestor’s personal information may be at risk.

**_Verification_**. Before responding to your request, we must first verify your identity using the Personal Information you recently provided to us. You must provide us with your full name, email address you used to contact us, and your address (if applicable). We will take steps to verify your request by matching the information provided by you with the information we have in our records. In some cases, we may request more information to verify your identity or where necessary to process your request. If we are unable to verify your identity after a good faith attempt, we may deny the request and, if so, will explain the basis for denial.

**California “Shine the Light” Disclosure**

California's "Shine the Light" law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83) permits users of our Sites and Services who are California residents to request, once per calendar year, certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information (if any) to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us using the contact information provided below. Please include in your request a current California address and your attestation that you are a California resident.

9\. Additional U.S. State Privacy Disclosures
---------------------------------------------

If you live in Colorado (effective July 1, 2023), Connecticut (effective July 1, 2023), Utah (effective December 31, 2023), or Virginia (effective January 1, 2023), you may have these rights:

* (1) The right to confirm whether Redfin is processing your Personal Information, and to access your Personal Information.
* (2) The right to request we correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information.
* (3) The right to request we delete your Personal Information.
* (4) The right to request a copy of the Personal Information you provided to us.
* (5) The right to opt out of (i) processing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising purposes, (ii) the sale of your Personal Information, and (iii) profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects.

To exercise rights (1) through (4), please contact us at [privacy@redfin.com](mailto:privacy@redfin.com). For right 5(iii), please note Redfin does not use Personal Information for profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects. Therefore, the consumer rights that apply to such decisions are not applicable to Redfin.

To exercise the right to opt-out of the processing of your Personal Information for targeted advertising purposes, please [click here to visit our page that explains your opt-out choices](https://www.redfin.com/about/privacy/cookie).

Redfin does not sell your Personal Information for monetary consideration; to the extent that our data sharing for targeted advertising purposes constitutes a “sale” under the above state privacy laws, click the link provided immediately above if you wish to exercise your opt-out rights.

Depending on your state of residence, you may have the right to appeal our decision to refuse to act based on your request. To do so, please contact us at [privacy@redfin.com](mailto:privacy@redfin.com) and attach or include information related to your original request.

10\. Other Important Information
--------------------------------

### A. Children

Our Sites and Services are not directed to children under 13 (or other age as defined by local law), and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children. If you learn that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, you may contact us at the email address below with the subject line "COPPA Child Information Request." If we learn that we have collected any Personal Information from a child in violation of applicable law, we will promptly take steps to delete such information.

### B. Supervisory Authority

If you are located in the European Economic Area, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you believe our processing of your Personal Information violates applicable law.

### C. Links to Third Party Sites/Applications

The Services may contain links to other websites/applications and other websites/applications may reference or link to our Sites or other Services. These other websites and applications are not controlled by us. We encourage our users to read the privacy policies of each website and application with which they interact. Redfin does not endorse, screen or approve, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites or applications. Visiting these other websites or applications is at your own risk.

### D. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Redfin may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion. If there are any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you as required by applicable law, which may include updating our notice on our Sites. You understand that you will be deemed to have accepted the updated Privacy Policy if you continue to use the Services after the new Privacy Policy takes effect.

### E. Contact Us

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Attn:  
Legal Dept  
Redfin Corporation  
1099 Stewart Street, Suite 600  
Seattle, WA 98101

© 2024 Redfin. All rights reserved.

California DRE #01521930

Redfin is licensed to do business in New York as Redfin Real Estate. [NY Standard Operating Procedures](https://redfin.widen.net/s/c2njc52hnk/redfin_new-york-standardized-operating-procedures "NY Standard Operating Procedures")

New Mexico [Real Estate Licenses](https://ssl.cdn-redfin.com/vLATEST/images/nm-licenses/redfin_new_mexico_licenses.pdf "New Mexico Real Estate Licenses")

TREC: [Info About Brokerage Services](https://ssl.cdn-redfin.com/vLATEST/images/about/ibs-statement/texas.pdf), [Consumer Protection Notice](https://www.trec.texas.gov/forms/consumer-protection-notice)

If you are using a screen reader, or having trouble reading this website, please call Redfin Customer Support for help at [1-844-759-7732](tel:1-844-759-7732).

[](https://www.redfin.com/about/terms-of-use#Equal_Housing_Opportunity)REDFIN IS COMMITTED TO AND ABIDES BY THE FAIR HOUSING ACT AND EQUAL OPPORTUNITY ACT. READ REDFIN'S [FAIR HOUSING POLICY](https://www.redfin.com/about/fair-housing-policy) AND THE [NEW YORK STATE FAIR HOUSING NOTICE](https://www.dos.ny.gov/licensing/docs/FairHousingNotice_new.pdf).
